foxcareers.com 2018-09-23

# Privacy Statement | 21st Century Fox Careers

## 21st Century Fox Careers Privacy Statement

**Last Updated: May 2018**

**Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., Fox Entertainment Group, LLC, Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation, Fox Networks Group and their affiliates** (collectively “ **Fox** ”) value your trust and are committed to the responsible management, use and protection of personal information. This privacy statement (the “ **Statement** ”) describes our practices in connection with all the information that we collect through the careers website located at www.21CFCareers.com, through posting on various job boards that push candidates to https://21cf4.wd2.myworkdayjobs-impl.com (“Careers Sites”), and offline in connection with your application for a job, position or internship with Fox. **Personal information submitted elsewhere, outside the Careers Sites, will be used in accordance with those websites’ privacy statements.**

Please read this Statement carefully prior to submitting any personal information. You must create a candidate profile account in order to apply for a position within Fox via the Careers Sites. 

## Table of Contents:

  * Who is responsible for your personal information?
  * Information We Collect
  * Use of Information
  * Disclosure of Personal Information
  * Data Retention
  * Activity Information Collection: Cookies and Similar Technologies
  * Access and Correction
  * Security
  * Links to Third-Party Websites
  * Data Transfers and Applicable Job Application Law
  * About Children
  * Your Rights under GDPR
  * Changes to the Policy
  * Contact Us

## Who is responsible for your personal information?

The Careers Sites allow you to apply for jobs at Fox worldwide, as a benefit of Fox’s global recruitment function. This means that personal information you submit to Fox will be used by Fox’s global recruitment functions located in the United States, as well as by Fox affiliates across the world, depending on the position you apply for. Therefore, this Statement refers to the collection and use of your personal data performed by **Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., Fox Entertainment Group, LLC, Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation, and Fox Networks Group, with offices at 1211 Avenue of the Americas, New York, NY 10036 and 2121 Avenue of the Stars, Los Angeles, California, 90067 (in their capacity as “joint controllers”) -** where Fox’s global recruiting function resides and from where Career Sites are managed - as well as by **any other relevant Fox affiliate, that may need to access the information, depending on the position you are applying for. The complete list of Fox affiliates** that may process your information in their capacity of data controllers is available [here](http://www.21cf.com/). As a potential employer, the relevant Fox affiliate will handle your personal information in accordance with this Statement. Any subsequent hiring or other employment-related decisions will be made by the Fox hiring affiliate in accordance with the laws of the country where the job will be located and a separate employee privacy policy will be provided, if required by applicable data protection law. 

For any information regarding this Statement and the use of your personal information by Fox (including any relevant Fox affiliate), you may contact us at [FoxCareersPrivacy@fox.com](mailto:FoxCareersPrivacy@fox.com). 

## Information We Collect

### Information You Provide

We may collect the following information from you in connection with your application:

  * Name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other contact information;
  * Username and password;
  * Work authorization status;
  * CV, résumé, cover letter, previous work experience and education information;
  * Skills;
  * Professional and other work-related licenses, permits and certifications held;
  * Information relating to references;
  * Any other information you elect to provide to us (e.g., employment preferences, willingness to relocate, desired salary, awards or professional memberships).

Any information you submit through the Careers Sites must be true, complete and not misleading. Submitting inaccurate, incomplete, or misleading information may lead to a rejection of your application during the application process or disciplinary action including immediate termination of employment. In addition, it is your responsibility to ensure that information you submit does not violate any third party’s rights. 

If you provide us with personal information of a reference or any other individual as part of your application, it is your responsibility to obtain consent from that individual prior to providing the information to us. 

### Information from Other Sources

Fox may obtain information about you from other sources, such as from your references in connection with your application, as permitted by applicable law, or other information such as background checks, as permitted by applicable law. 

### SENSITIVE INFORMATION

**Please do not submit any information that could be considered “sensitive personal data.”** Sensitive personal data includes personal data regarding your racial or ethnic origin; your political opinions, religious beliefs or other beliefs of a similar nature; whether you are a member of a trade union; data regarding your physical or mental health or condition; your sexual orientation; and data regarding the commission or alleged commission of any criminal offense. 

Only for certain limited positions and/or in selected jurisdictions, you may be asked to provide certain sensitive personal data, such as identification of veteran status or information relating to convictions of a criminal offense, to the extent provided and authorized by the applicable law. 

## Use of Information

The information that you submit on the Careers Sites will be used **to consider your application for the specific position you applied for** and in particular to: (a) process your application; (b) to assess your capabilities and qualifications for a job; and (c) to respond to your inquiries and communicate with you about your application. 

If we hire you, personal information we collect in connection with your application also may be used to pre-populate some fields in our human resources system. Any such information may become part of your employee file and will be subject to Fox's privacy statement for employees, if required under applicable data protection laws. You will be allowed to amend this information at any time. 

We will use your information as permitted by local law, **to protect our rights** including to: (a) enforce this Statement; (b) to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (c) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

Where required, we will use such information to: 

  * **comply with or monitor compliance with any applicable law or regulation; and to**
  * **respond to requests from public and government authorities,** including public and government authorities outside your country of residence. 

Providing personal information to us through the Careers Sites is necessary for us to fulfill all of the purposes listed above. If you fail to provide sufficient information, Fox may be unable to consider your employment application. 

Please note, that your personal information also will be **used for Fox’s global personnel recruiting function, should your profile be suitable for positions other than the one for which you applied.** In such case, the information about you will be added to Fox’s international candidate database and may be used to consider you for opportunities at Fox and its affiliates other than the one(s) for which you applied. Such additional processing will be carried out with your consent, if such consent is required by applicable law, or on the basis of Fox’s legitimate interest in maintaining applicants’ records to facilitate recruiting within its global operations; such legitimate interest is adequately balanced with your interest in being considered for other positions that may suit and interest you. If you no longer wish to be considered for other positions within Fox, contact us by email or mail using the details in the “Contact Us” section below. In particular, if you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you can withdraw your consent or object at any time to this activity as described in the “Your Rights under GDPR” section of this Statement. 

Finally, your personal data may be used by Fox to complete a corporate transaction, such as a proposed or actual reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Fox businesses, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). Such activity also is performed on the basis of the legitimate interest of Fox and its possible counterparties to perform such economic activities (corporate transactions). That interest is adequately balanced with your interest, since the data processing is performed within the limits strictly necessary to perform such economic activities. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, this data processing activity is not mandatory and you can object at any time, as described in the section of this Statement titled “Your Rights under GDPR”. 

##  Disclosure of Personal Information 

Fox may share personal information with its **Fox affiliates** that are involved in evaluating candidates for a given position. Fox will make the information available to personnel with a business need to know the information, including personnel in the recruiting, human resources and information technology departments, and in the department responsible for the position(s) for which you are applying or for which you are being considered. The complete list of Fox affiliates is available [ here](http://21cf.com/). 

Fox may share personal information with **our third-party service providers,** who provide services such as hosting and operating the Careers Sites, recruiting assistance, background checks, processing and similar services. Such third party service providers and professional advisors may process personal information if they have a written contract with Fox and are expected to comply with applicable data protection law and to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information. 

To the extent necessary, Fox may transfer your personal information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our businesses, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

## Data Retention

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Statement and in accordance with our records retention policies, which is currently **three years** for the EEA countries. After this period, your personal information will be deleted from our systems, except for: (i) longer periods where the retention of information is necessary due to litigation or other legal proceedings, requests from competent government authorities, or in compliance with applicable laws; or (ii) shorter periods where required by applicable law. 

#### Activity Information Collection: Cookies and Similar Technologies

When you access and interact with the Careers Sites, Fox and its service providers may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Careers Sites, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Careers Sites from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, or other information for that device. Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a unique identifier. Our websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer or other device so the website or app can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Careers Sites, such as pages you have visited. By collecting and using this data, we hope to improve the quality of the Careers Sites. The data collected through the use of tracking technologies will not be kept for longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes specified in this Statement. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html. For further information on deleting, disabling or blocking cookies please visit www.allaboutcookies.org or http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the Careers Sites. 

Third parties that support the Careers Site by providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information when you use the Careers Site or third-party services. Fox does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. 

Third parties that support the Careers Site by providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information when you use the Careers Site or third-party services. Fox does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. 

Please visit our Cookie Policy for more information. 

**Do Not Track Signals for the US applicants.** At this time, we do not respond to browser 'Do Not Track' signals, as we await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted. 

#### Access and Correction

If you register on the Careers Sites, you may access, review, and change your personal information stored therein by logging into the Careers Sites and updating your account information. Please note that if you change or correct information after submitting it through the Careers Sites, such changes will be visible to Fox. The updated profile will be used as the default the next time you apply for a job using your account online. To change personal information that you have already submitted for consideration for a specific position, please update your profile. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. 

Apart from information contained in your profile, you may request access to personal information we collect, or its modification or suppression, where permitted by applicable law. Please contact us by email or mail using the details in the “Contact Us” section below with any such requests. In your request, please make clear what personal information you would like to access or have changed, whether you would like to have personal information that you have provided to us suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your personal information. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that certain personal information may be exempt from such access, correction, or suppression rights pursuant to local data protection laws. 

## Security

Fox has implemented reasonable and appropriate measures to protect personal information that are consistent with applicable privacy and data security laws and regulations, including measures to protect personal information from misuse or accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, acquisition or access. 

If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account. 

For any questions, you can contact us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section below. 

## Links to Third-Party Websites

The Careers Sites may contain links to other websites. This Statement does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information, or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any website or service to which the Careers Sites link. The inclusion of a link on the Careers Sites does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by Fox or our affiliates. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on those sites, including their privacy policies. 

## Data Transfers and Applicable Job Application Law

The Careers Sites allow you to apply for jobs at Fox world-wide, as a benefit of Fox’s global recruitment function. This means that personal information you submit to Fox may be available to Fox personnel and departments located in other countries. The Careers Sites are hosted in the United States. Fox uses third party service providers in connection with the Career Sites. Accordingly, you acknowledge that any personal information you submit to us through the Careers Sites will be transferred to the United States and other countries in or outside the European Economic Area. The level of protection of personal data in these countries may be different from the protection offered in the country where you reside. Please note that we have adopted appropriate safeguards to protect your personal information regardless of where it resides, such as the Standard Contractual Clauses adopted by the European Commission, in case of personal data referring to residents of the European Economic Area. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the right at any time to request a copy of such safeguards, according to the “Your rights under GDPR” section below. 

## About Children

The Careers Sites are not intended for children under the age of 16. 

## Your rights under GDPR

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you are entitled to the rights provided for by the European General Data Protection Regulation no. 679/2016 (“ **GDPR** ”). In particular, you have the right, at any given time, to: 

  * a) obtain confirmation as to whether or not your personal data exists and to be informed of its content and source, verify its accuracy and request its rectification, update or amendment (see also the “Access and Correction” section of this Statement); 
  * b) request the deletion, anonymization or restriction of the processing of your personal data processed in breach of the applicable law; 
  * c) request that Fox limit the processing of your personal data where: 
    * You contest the accuracy of the personal data until we have taken sufficient steps to correct or verify its accuracy;
    * the processing is unlawful but you do not want us to erase the data; 
    * we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but you require it for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims; or 
  * d) withdraw your consent to the processing of personal data, if such processing is based on your consent; 
  * e) object to the processing of your personal data, when the processing is based on the legitimate interest of Fox. Upon your objection, Fox shall no longer process the personal data unless Fox demonstrates (i) compelling legitimate grounds for the processing that override your interests, rights and freedoms or (ii) that the processing of the data is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; 
  * f) restrict Fox’s processing of your personal data when that processing is based on Fox’s legitimate interests and where you have objected to the processing on those grounds pending verification as to whether Fox has compelling legitimate grounds to continue the processing; 
  * g) request the erasure of your personal data without undue delay; 
  * h) “data portability”, namely to receive an electronic copy of your personal data that you have provided to us when (i) that data is being processed by automatic means, and (ii) the processing is either based upon your consent or necessary for the performance of a contract with you; 
  * i) lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority of your country; 
  * j) in case of transfer of personal data to countries that do not offer an adequate level of protection with respect to the protection of personal data, you have the right at any time to request a copy of the safeguards adopted by Fox to protect your personal data. 

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you can exercise the above rights by sending a request to Fox at the contact details indicated in the “Contact Us” section below. 

## Changes to this Statement

We reserve the right to amend this Statement at any time in order to address future developments of Fox, the Careers Sites or changes in industry or legal trends. We will post the revised version on the Careers Sites. You can determine when the Statement was revised by referring to the “Last Updated” legend on the top of this Statement. Any changes will become effective upon the posting of the revised Statement on the Careers Sites. By continuing to use the Careers Sites following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Statement, in whole or part, you can choose not to continue using the Careers Sites. 

## Contact Us

If you have questions or requests, please feel free to contact us at [FoxCareersPrivacy@fox.com](mailto:FoxCareersPrivacy@fox.com) or by mail at 2121 Avenue of the Stars, Los Angeles, California, 90067, Attention Privacy Office.
